

Taylor Wright

Full Stack Web Developer

With a 14-year history of high-level customer service in a fast paced, creative environment, I have built a career focused on sales, retention, and resolutions. Looking to broaden my career scope and bring my strong dedication, responsibility, and motivation while utilizing my Full Stack Web Development certificate obtained through the University of Denver.



(719) 453-8516



tjwri25@gmail.com



@Taylor-J-Wright



https://tjwri25.github.io/portfolio/

Work Experience

En Gedi Salon | Nov 2013 - Present Independent Hairstylist

- Managing my own business, with a high level of customer service
- Maintaining my schedule, clients, inventory, and finances from beginning to end

Floyd's 99 Barbershop | Aug 2009 - Present Hairstylist

- Building relationships with clients, in a fast-paced environment
- Translated client requests into polished, high-level styles

Just Associates, Inc. | Aug 2016 - June 2019 Patient Identity Expert - Level 4

 High attention to detail, determining medical record's eligibility to be merged

cont'd

- Experience with multiple databases and client systems, including: EPIC, Nextgate, All Scripts, Soarian, Meditech, and Cerner
- High attention to detail, determining medical record's eligibility to be merged
- I was consistently chosen for increasingly difficult projects due to my high level of accuracy, and timely manner of completion

Great Clips | Apr 2008 - Aug 2009 Assistant Manager

- I was quickly promoted to Assistant Manager due to my reliability, and consistent dedication to customer service
- Handling scheduling for the shop, customer relations, and providing employees constructive feedback, and achievable goals

Educational History

University of Denver Bootcamps | Dec 2020 - June 2021 Full Stack Web Development

Toni & Guy Hairdressing Academy | 2006 -2007 Hairstylist License

> Ponderosa High School | 2002 -2006 High School Diploma

Skills Summary

- Customer Service
- Web Development
- HTML
- Cascading Style Sheets (CSS)
- JavaScript
- Node.js
- MySQL
- MongoDB
- React.js
- Sales
- Data Entry
- Data Analysis
- Electronic Medical Record (EMR)